Hey everyone, this is Noguchi from Equal Love. Just a quick note today.
I'm visiting Kurosawa Gakki-san, where there are many instruments!
Why am I visiting Kurosawa Gakki?
I'm in the guitar department, and here we have a bass guitar department.
I'm thinking of starting either one of them.
Wow... I don't know...
I'm thinking of doing tours, anniversary concerts...
I thought it would be great if we could liven up our live performances.
I thought it would be great if we could add more excitement to our live shows.
And what a surprise...
Even though we're not in the boat racing club...
Mr. Sazehara is here!
Hello!
I'm going to the boat race club.
You're going?
Let's go.
I'll go with you.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Today...
I'm only here to buy it today.
I bought a credit card.
I'm already planning this, but I'll buy it.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
I'm under a lot of pressure to do it, pressure to make sure I'm doing it.
I'll do my best... then let's look for an instrument of your choice... which would be better... bass or guitar?
I like the way your fingers sound... but in a live setting...
But in a live setting, I'd rather play the guitar.
So I think it's true.
This is what is called "jazz bass".
This is the form that is most commonly used.
I think looks are important, so why don't you have one of these at home?
That's for sure.
But I think I like the black one.
Black is cool.
Black? What's the best part about black?
It's heavy! Is it? It's pretty heavy.
But it looks good on you! Does it look good on me? I'm so happy!
Wow!
It's heavy.
It's a little narrower than a guitar.
I see.
You're right.
Wait, wait, wait. Which one?
What do I do?
How do we do it? Who decides? This one.
Who decides?
Me?
Well, let me hold your guitar... one time.
And the guitar, please.
Yes, thank you.
Oh, yes.
But it's really heavy.
Ahhh...
About 3.5 kg.
Isn't it cool? I don't know...
Is it cool?
Yeah, it is.
Which one?
Seriously, I don't care either way.
I don't know.
IORI fans are going to be happy with the base.
I know!
I'm sure the guitarists will be happy too.
In the future...
In the future, when I'm going to do a solo
I think it will be easier to sing.
I think it's the guitar that's more glamorous, but Iori's fans really feel that Iori is great as a bass player.
I really feel the same way.
Can you play it?
Let's give it a try.
Let's sit down.
Like this? Okay.
There you go.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
I can see it... the FNS.
No, is that too much? That was amazing.
That's so cool!
It's cool.
I'm having so much fun.
I feel like I can play already.
Can I have a little bass?
Sounds cool.
Bass is cool.
What kind of dance?
The bass is so cool.
If I hear this sound now
I want Yuri to make this sound
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've been thinking that too
Me too.
I've been thinking that, too.
I think so, too. I don't know what to do.
Oh, hey!
I'm sorry to push you... but you're so cool.
It's so hard to figure out.
I don't know... Iori's totally this... a bass guitar... so cool!
How's it going? What do you think?
I think bass guitar is cool... but I think it's better if you really want to play. Either way, it's exciting.
But when you play it and the guitar sounds better
I feel like I'm playing an instrument, and it feels good, but I'd rather play the bass guitar.
I've always wanted to play bass, and when I play it, I feel
I don't know.
I have more desire to play the bass guitar.
Oh, really.
I see.
Maybe I want to play bass.
If you're okay with bass.
Oh...
If that's what you've always wanted to do, maybe it's better for you.
What's more, it looks good on you.
What do you have in black?
That one's just as good.
I like that one.
For a matte lover.
Me too.
I like that one the best.
Okay, I'm with you on this one.
That's fast...
-8.5 is so light. -It's so light! It's light, and it's matte, which is cool!
-It's so light. -Oh, it's light! Really? It's totally different from this one.
-It's so light. -I think it's good!
-It's good! It's good! -Yeah! It's so cool!
-Yeah! -I loved it. I loved this one.
-Love at first sight. -Let's do it, then!
-This one? -Let's hear some sound. This way.
-That's great! -Wow!
adventure time
Wow.
Cool!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wow, that's good.
This is cool, this is what I like. Okay, let's get some of that and some equipment.
I don't care. I'll get the one Ion likes. I don't know what I'll do.
I don't know. Maybe this one.
Let's go with that for now.
We can change it in the future to match the costumes and stuff.
That's right.
Let's practice in secret.
Yeah.
So that we don't get caught.
Secret.
That's right.
It's a secret!
I only use it for boat races.
This savings account for my boat races.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
Thank you for watching.
We've decided on this base. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Mr. Shibahara, of course.
I told you this earlier, but maybe...
Some might say it's too good for beginners.
But we made it so that you can use it forever. Please take good care of it.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll practice hard for the 7th anniversary concert.
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
This January, YUJI said he wanted to start playing the bass guitar by himself.
He's been working with us for the past six months.
I'm sure you've always wanted to play your own bass guitar in front of the audience.
I'm sure you've always wanted to play your own bass in front of the audience.
Mie Sasahara made up the setlist for Coal Love's 7th anniversary concert at K-ARENA.
In the band corner, Ms. Noguchi performed her center piece, "Nonoppe Nonoppe Nonoppe".
Nonoppe nonoppe nonoppe, which is his debut as a bass player.
I'm glad that you made such a place for us, so let's do our best!
I'll do my best.
Yes, I understand.
Yes, sir.
How about your confidence?
I don't have it!
Eight songs in front of 20,000 people.
Oh no! I'm at 7 or 8...oh no, what am I going to do? Oh, my God, what am I going to do?
Also, it's been about two months, so I'm going to play one song in front of more than 10,000 people, and I'm going to play it well. Two more months, I guess.
Let's practice hard and decide on this berth.
Yes, I will do my best. Thank you very much.
Yes, I will.
Is this okay?
Yes, sir.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm good.
Not even one point?
Ha-ha-ha.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm.
Uh-oh.
If I can find an assignment today.
Yeah.
First things first.
3 Leader Vibes
The Heart
Crow.
Too different from what I usually practice at home, hand sweat slipping.
Oh no!
Music
I can't even say this, so...
Thanks for your hard work
I feel like it's going to be a song
It's going fast
I'll do my best
It's cool.
I can't wait to see what you do
Hmmm...
How was it?
It's cool.
You look great.
I thought it must have been a lot of work.
A lot of people put on security to make sure they all go.
Only 4 of us could go.
I was too nervous to pull it off.
You were nervous, weren't you?
You can go.
Really?
Next rehearsal, Shukiri, give it some thought.
Are you sure?
We'll do our best.
I'm nervous.
When we did it...
I was sweating during the song.
I was sweating from moving around, and my hands were sweating from nerves.
I was slipping all over the place.
I was sweating so much that I had to get over it.
But the staff put a towel on the microphone.
I hope I'll be able to perform with confidence on the day of the show.
But, you know, it's a celebration, so first of all, happy birthday!
I'm going to enjoy myself, and of course, I'm going to enjoy myself.
Let's go, let's do our best!
Dreamer I'll hold you in the back of my mind, remembering after the sky in the room
I will love you forever
It's over, Day 1!
Thank you for watching!
I was so nervous!
I didn't know what to do.
But
I think I did what I had to do.
Do you remember when you were playing?
No.
But...
And...
After I told her she was a nice girl, one of the members came close to me, and I glanced over and saw Miri's eyes.
She looked at me with a big smile on her face.
And all my nervousness and anxiety went away.
I felt like I was having a great time.
I was so happy to see her.
but also the power of the members is really amazing.
I was so glad that everyone was there.
It was a lot of fun.
The downside?
A drawback!
Tomorrow...
I want 80.
I thought 80 was 100.
I'm not sure about 100.
I don't know, it's kind of hard.
Plus 27 points.
Yes, sir.
I'll try to get to 100.
I'm going for it.
I'll enjoy it.
Thank you very much
Thank you for your hard work.